Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Photographs PC0062
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Photographs, Accession ARCH-2008-194
  - Additional Slides
    - Presentations (Box 10)
    - SEQ (Box 11)
    - Systems -- Parking (Box 11)
    - Systems -- Circulation (Box 11)
    - Systems -- Landscape (Box 11)
    - Life (Box 11)
    - Systems -- Site furnishing (Box 12)
    - Systems -- Artwork (Box 12)
    - Systems -- Building (Box 12)
    - Scanned images, 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
      Scope and Contents note
      Aerials, Campus Planning, Dream Team, Historic, Land Use, Life, Plans -- Land Use, Presentations, Sand Hill Road and 2) SEQ, Serra, Systems -- circulation, Systems -- landscape, Systems -- parking, and other Systems
      - AERIALS
        - 01 - CAMPUS CENTER
        - 02 - CAMPUS LANDS - CENTRAL CAMPUS
        - 03 - CAMPUS CENTER
        - 04 - AERIALS - DAPER-Q13
        - 05 - AERIALS - OBLIQUE - SEQ
        - 06 - AERIALS
        - 07 - AERIALS - OBLIQUE - SEQ
        - 08 - AERIALS - OBLIQUE - SEQ
        - 09 - AERIALS - OBLIQUE - GATES SEQ
        - 10 - AERIALS - EAST CAMPUS
        - 11 - AERIALS - GSB HOUSING - HILL HOUSING
        - 12 - AERIALS - MED CENTER - SAND HILL
        - 13 - AERIALS - MED CENTER - SAND HILL
        - 14 - AERIALS - FOOTHILLS
        - 15 - AERIALS - FOOTHILLS
        - 16 - AERIALS - Q90
        - 17 - AERIALS - SLAC - ARILLAGA
        - 18 - AERIALS
      - CAMPUS PLANNING
        - 01 - 1997 CAMPUS PLAN
        - 02 - 1997 CAMPUS PLAN
        - 03 - 1997 CAMPUS PLAN
        - 04 - 1997 CAMPUS PLAN
        - 05 - 1997 SWA CAMPUS PLAN
        - 06 - 1997 SWA CAMPUS PLAN
        - 07 - SWA CAMPUS PLAN A+B
        - 08 - SWA CAMPUS PLAN B+C
        - 09 - CENTRAL CAMPUS PLAN - SEBASTIAN & ASSOC 04-98
        - 10 - CAMPUS PLANNING - BILL JOHNSON - LAURIE OLIN
        - 11 - CAMPUS PLNG - FRAMEWORK - AXIAL VISTAS
        - 12 - CAMPUS PLNG - 2nd CENT
        - 13 - CAMPUS PLNG - 2nd CENT
        - 14 - CAMPUS PLNG - REGIONAL
        - 15 - CAMPUS PLNG - LANDSCAPE PLANS
        - 16 - CAMPUS PLNG - PALO ALTO - STANFORD FORUM
        - 17 - CAMPUS PLNG - SYSTEMS
        - 18 - CAMPUS PLNG - TEXTS
        - 19 - CAMPUS PLNG - MISC
      - DREAM TEAM
        - 01 - DREAM TEAM
        - 02 - DREAM TEAM
        - 03 - DREAM TEAM
        - 04 - DREAM TEAM
      - HISTORIC
        - 01 - H-PLANS - OLMSTED - MISC PLANS
        - 02 - H-PLANS - OLMSTED - MISC PLANS & DRWs
        - 03 - H-AERIAL - CAMPUS PRE-1930s
        - 04 - H-AERIAL - CAMPUS 1930s-1960s
        - 05 - H-PLANS - CAMPUS DWS 1920'S
        - 06 - H-PLANS - CAMPUS DWS
        - 07 - H-1906 - 1906 EARTHQUAKE EFFECTS
        - 08 - H-REF - PLANNING - MISC
        - 09 - H-REF - ARCHITECTURAL - MISC
        - 10 - NO LABEL
        - 11 - H-REF - CAMPUS - ILLUSTRATIONS
        - 12 - H-LIFE - CAMPUS - MISC 1950-70
        - 13 - H-LIFE - CAMPUS - MISC 1930-
        - 14 - HQ01 - MEM. CHURCH - PRE-1906 QUAKE
        - 15 - H-Q01 - INNER QUAD - PRE-1906 QUAKE
        - 16 - H-Q01 - MAIN QUAD - LANDSCAPE - 1910's
        - 17 - H-Q02 - CAMPUS - MISC - 1906
        - 18 - H-Q07 - OLD CHEMISTRY - PRE-1906 QUAKE
        - 19 - H-Q08 - OLD LIBRARY - MAUSOLEUM - 1905-06
        - 20 - H-Q11 - THE ROW - PALM DR - MISC
        - 21 - H-Q14 - CAMPUS - MISC
      - LAND USE
        - 01 - LUP USE PERMIT
        - 02 - REGIONS - PLANS - 85-87
        - 03 - REGIONS - PLANS - 85
        - 04 - CAMPUS LAND USE
        - 05 - LOCATIONS - CITIES LAND USE
        - 06 - LUP - LAND USE AND CIRCULAT
        - 07 - SUITABILITY ANALYSIS - OTHER
        - 08 - OPEN SPACE
        - 09 - HIST - LAND USE HISTORY
      - LIFE
        - 01 - LIFE - 100 YEARS
        - 02 - CAMPUS LIFE
        - 03 - CAMPUS LIFE - 100 YEARS
        - 04 - LIFE - QUAD
      - PLANS - LAND USE
        - 01 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUP 1997-99
        - 02 - CAMPUS PLNG - 10 YEAR PLAN - 1991
        - 03 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 93
        - 04 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 90s
        - 05 - REPORTS - PLANS - 1990 LAND USE PLAN
        - 06 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 80s
        - 07 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 80s
        - 08 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 1971
        - 09 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 70s
        - 10 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 70s
        - 11 - CAMPUS PLNG - LUPS 60s
        - 12 - L.U.P. PRESENTATION - MAPS & TEXT
        - 13 - L.U.P. PRESENTATION - MAPS & TEXT
        - 14 - L.U.P. PRESENTATION - MAPS & TEXT
        - 15 - L.U.P. PRESENTATION - MAPS & TEXT
      - PRESENTATIONS
        - 01 - PRESENTATION TEXTS
        - 02 - PRESENTATION - SITE FURNISHINGS
        - 03 - PRESENTATION - SITE FURNISHINGS
        - 04 - PRESENTATION TEXTS
        - 05 - PRESENTATION TEXTS
        - 06 - PRESENTATION TEXT
        - 07 - NO LABEL
        - 08 - HP 4-10-95 PRESENTATION ORIGINALS
        - 09 - NO LABEL
        - 10 - THEN-NOW PRESENTATION 1979
        - 11 - QUAD SLIDE SHOW 9-15-78
        - 12 - QUAD SLIDE SHOW 9-15-78
        - 13 - NO LABEL
        - 14 - PRESENTATION
        - 15 - Q07 - UCSF-S - 02-97 A.C.B
        - 16 - Q07 - SUMC - 02-97 - A.C.B
        - 17 - Q07 - SUMC - 02-97 - A.C.B
        - 18 - NO LABEL
        - 19 - JUDY'S PRESENTATION
        - 20 - GRAPHICS - DRAFT, PRESENTATION
        - 21 - PRESENTATION - GRAPHICS - TEXT
        - 22 - NO LABEL
        - 23 - NO LABEL
        - 24 - PRESENTATION - PAT SAW
        - 25 - NO LABEL
        - 26 - PRESENTATION - NWC. CONECT. - ELEM. PROG
        - 27 - PRESENTATION - NWC. CONECT. - ELEM. PROG
        - 28 - NO LABEL
        - 29 - PRESENTATION - NWC. CONECT. - ELEM. PROG
        - 30 - NO LABEL
      - SAND HILL ROAD
        - 01 - SHR - ROAD EXT
        - 02 - SAND HILL- WALKER J&P
        - 03 - NO LABEL
        - 04 - SAND HILL - WALKERJ&P
        - 05 - NO LABEL
        - 06 - NO LABEL
        - 07 - SHR - COMMUNITY
      - SEQ
        - 01 - SEQ PRESENTATION
        - 02 - NO LABEL
        - 03 - NO LABEL
        - 04 - NO LABEL
        - 05 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 06 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 07 - SEQ (PRE) ELEVATIONS - CONNECTIVE ELEMENTS
        - 08 - SEQ (PRE) PLANS-ELE, CONNECTIVE ELEMENTS
        - 09 - SEQ (PRE) ELEVATIONS, SECTIONS
        - 10 - SEQ (PRE) CONNECTIVE ELEMENTS DIAGRAMS
        - 11 - SEQ (PRE) SECTIONS, ELEVATIONS
        - 12 - SEQ (PRE) RENDERINGS
        - 13 - SEQ (PRE) PLANS, DIAGRAMS
        - 14 - SEQ (PRE) DIAGRAMS
        - 15 - SEQ (PRE) DIAGRAMS
        - 16 - SEQ (PRE) PLANS
        - 17 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 18 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 19 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 20 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS
        - 21 - PRE - SEQ
        - 22 - NO LABEL
        - 23 - SEQ (PRE) MODEL - Q4
        - 24 - NO LABEL
        - 25 - SEQ MODEL - Q4 - DUPS - 9-20-94
        - 26 - SEQ (PRE) MODEL - Q4 - EXISTING CONDITIONS - 5-25-94 & 6-9-94
        - 27 - SEQ MODEL - Q4 - 9-20-94
        - 28 - NO LABEL
        - 29 - NO LABEL
        - 30 - SEQ (PRE) Q4 - CONNECTIVE ELEVATION DRWGS - 2-88
        - 31 - SEQ (PRE) DRAWINGS - VARIOUS DATES
        - 32 - SEQ (PRE) MISC. - VARIOUS DATES
        - 33 - SEQ - TREES - 1996
        - 34 - SEQ - SITE VIEW - 11-95
        - 35 - SEQ (PRE) SITE VIEW
        - 36 - SEQ (PRE) AERIAL PHOTOS
        - 37 - SEQ (PRE) AERIAL PHOTOS
        - 38 - SEQ
        - 39 - NO LABEL
        - 40 - SEQ - MODELS
        - 41 - SEQ - MODELS
        - 42 - SEQ - MODELS
        - 43 - SEQ - SITE VIEW MODELS
        - 44 - SEQ - MODELS - DAVID 10-95
        - 45 - SEQ - MODELS
        - 46 - SEQ - MODELS - DAVID 10-95
        - 47 - SEQ - TREES @ BOETHING TREELAND
        - 48 - SEQ - MODEL - 10-95
        - 49 - SEQ (PRE) 3-90 SERRA CONNECTING PLAN
        - 50 - SEQ (PRE) 3-90 SERRA CONNECTING PLAN
        - 51 - SEQ (PRE) MODEL - ARCADE
        - 52 - SEQ (PRE) NWC PHII - 9-86
        - 53 - SEQ (PRE) NWC MISC. - 1986
        - 54 - SEQ (PRE) NWC PH.I - 9-86
        - 55 - SEQ (PRE) MISC
        - 56 - SEQ (PRE) 1988 - SECTION AXIS NS
        - 57 - SEQ (PRE) FEB. 1988 - INT ARCADES
        - 58 - SEQ (PRE) 1988 - ARCADE OPTIONS
        - 59 - SEQ (PRE) 1988
        - 60 - SEQ (PRE) 1988
        - 61 - SEQ - Q4 - NEAR W.C. - 06-92
        - 62 - SEQ - Q4 - NEAR W.C. - 09-90
        - 63 - SEQ - Q4 - MODEL - 04-92
        - 64 - SEQ (PRE) Q4 - PLANNING - 11-89
        - 65 - SEQ (PRE) Q4 - ARCADE STUDY - 02-88
        - 66 - SEQ (PRE) DUPES
        - 67 - SEQ (PRE) TEXT
        - 68 - SEQ (PRE) HP BLDG
        - 69 - SEQ
        - 70 - SEQ - CIRCULATION
        - 71 - SEQ (PRE) PLANS, RENDERINGS, DIAGRAMS
        - 72 - SEQ (PRE) DIAGRAMS, DRAWINGS
        - 73 - SEQ (PRE) PLANS
        - 74 - SEQ - DRAWINGS - PCF
        - 75 - NO LABEL
        - 76 - SEQ (PRE) AERIAL PHOTOS
        - 77 - SEQ (PRE) MODELS, PENDANT FIX, ARCADES
        - 78 - SEQ (PRE) TILT-UP TYPE BLDGS
      - SERRA
        - 01 - PROJECT - SERRA MALL - PHOTOS
        - 02 - QUAD 13 - SERRA STREET
        - 03 - PROJECT - SERRA MALL - PHOTOS
        - 04 - PROJECT - SERRA MALL
        - 05 - PROJECT - SERRA MALL - DRAWINGS
        - 06 - SERRA MALL - DRAWINGS
        - 07 - SERRA - SEBASTIAN & ASSOCIATES
        - 08 - SERRA ST. - MODELS
        - 09 - SERRA ST. - MODELS
        - 10 - SERRA ST. - MODELS
        - 11 - SERRA ST. - MODELS
        - 12 - SERRA ST. - MODELS
        - 13 - PROJECT - SERRA MALL - DRAWINGS
        - 14 - Q8 - TANNER FOUNTAIN CONSTRUCTION
        - 15 - SERRA FOUNTAIN MODELS
        - 16 - Q8 - SERRA FOUNTAIN CONSTRUCTION
        - 17 - SERRA PROJECT - MISC
        - 18 - SERRA HALL MODEL - 9-95
      - SYSTEMS - CIRCULATION
        - 01 - CIRCULATION - VEHICULAR
        - 02 - CENTRAL CAMPUS - SEBASTIAN & ASSOC 04-98
        - 03 - CIRCULATION - PRESENTATION
        - 04 - CIRCULATION - PRESENTATION
        - 05 - CIRCULATION - STUDY - PLAN - 1988
        - 06 - CIRCULATION - STUDY - PLAN - PAT DAWE
        - 07 - CIRCULATION - STUDY - PLAN - 1978
        - 08 - CIRCULATION - VEHICULAR
        - 09 - CIRCULATION - VEHICULAR
        - 10 - CIRCULATION - MARQUERITE ROUTES
        - 11 - CIRCULATION - BIKE
        - 12 - CIRCULATION - BIKE
        - 13 - CIRCULATION - BIKE
        - 14 - CIRCULATION - BIKE
      - SYSTEMS - LANDSCAPE
        - 01 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - SAN FRAN. CREEK
        - 02 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - SAN FRAN. CREEK
        - 03 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - SAN FRAN. CREEK
        - 04 - LANDSCAPE DESIGN 02-13-89
        - 05 - LANDSCAPE - MISC
        - 06 - LANDSCAPE - STUDY
        - 07 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION
        - 08 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - GATES
        - 09 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - GATES
        - 10 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - MEM. AUD - TRESSIDER
        - 11 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - GOVERNOR'S CORNER
        - 12 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - GOVERNOR'S CORNER
        - 13 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - HAMMER THROW
        - 14 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - SERRA MALL 07-97
        - 15 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - SERRA MALL
        - 16 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - STERN TO SEQ
        - 17 - LANDSCAPE - TREE RELOCATION - CLARK CTR TO ROAD
        - 18 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - CAMPUS DRIVE (BAND GRASS)
        - 19 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - ESCONDIDO VILLAGE
        - 20 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - ESCONDIDO VILLAGE
        - 21 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT
        - 22 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT
        - 23 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT
        - 24 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT
        - 25 - LANDSCAPE - ENVIRONMENT - CAMPUS DRIVE
      - SYSTEMS - PARKING
        - 01 - PARKING - SUMC
        - 02 - PARKING - SUMC
        - 03 - PARKING - SUMC
        - 04 - PARKING - SUMC
        - 05 - PARKING - STUDY
        - 06 - PARKING - STUDY
        - 07 - PARKING - STUDY
        - 08 - PARKING
        - 09 - Q8 - PARKING STRUCTURE
        - 10 - PARKING - ROBLE
        - 11 - PARKING - ROBLE
        - 12 - PARKING - GALVEZ
      - SYSTEMS - SITE FURNISHING, ARTWORK, BLDG., HARDSCAPE
        - 01 - VEG. MGT - PLANS
        - 02 - NO LABEL
        - 03 - ARTWORK - SCULPTURE - THE WALL + POSSIBLE SITES
        - 04 - ARTWORK - SCULPTURE - NEW GUINEA
        - 05 - FURNISHINGS - STANFORD SHOPPING CENTER
        - 06 - SITE FURNISHING
        - 07 - SITE FURNISHING
        - 08 - SITE FURNISHING - BENCHES
        - 09 - BUILDING - DETAILS
        - 10 - SITE FURNISHING - LIGHTING
        - 11 - HARDSCAPE
        - 12 - HARDSCAPE
        - 13 - ARTWORK - SCULPTURE - RODIN
        - 14 - ARTWORK - SCULPTURE
        - 15 - SITE FURNISHING - SIGNAGE
        - 16 - SITE FURNISHING - SIGNAGE
        - 17 - SITE FURNISHING - SIGNAGE
        - 18 - SITE FURNISHINGS
        - 19 - SITE FURNISHING - BIKE LOCKERS-RACKS
        - 20 - SITE FURNISHING - BIKE LOCKERS-RACKS
        - 21 - BLDG. ELEMENTS - COLONNADE STUDIES
        - 22 - BUILDING - ROOFS
        - 23 - BUILDING - ROOFS
- Additional Photographs, 1997; Accession ARCH-2010-048
  - Buck Estate Inventory: Notebook of color photographs of furniture, lamps, ceramics, artworks, and other furnishings, 1997 (Box 1)
- Additional Photographs, 1995-2000; Accession ARCH-2010-064
  - Photo album: Press Building Demolition R&B Equipment, 2000 June (Box 1)
  - Photo album: Stanford University Press Annex and Mechanical Engineering Projects DPR Construction, Inc, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Language Corner Building 260 Weekly Progress Photographs (two 3-ring notebooks), 1995-1996 (Box 2)
- Additional Photographs, Accession ARCH-2018-039
  - Serra Mall, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manzanita Dining Commons, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campus Slides, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campus Photographs, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 4)